[
    {
        "question": "What can I say except, 'You're welcome', for the tides, the sun, the _____",
        "answer1": "stars",
        "answer2": "sky",
        "answer3": "moon",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Go Greased Lightnin', you're coasting through the _____ lap trial",
        "answer1": "heat",
        "answer2": "pre",
        "answer3": "beat",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You just remember what your old _____ said, you've got a friend in me",
        "answer1": "bud",
        "answer2": "friend",
        "answer3": "pal",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Here come the Men in Black, Galaxy _____",
        "answer1": "protectors",
        "answer2": "defenders",
        "answer3": "conquerors",
        "correctAnswer": 2 
    },
    {
        "question": "His palms are sweaty, knees weak, arms are _____",
        "answer1": "weak",
        "answer2": "tired",
        "answer3": "heavy",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Now I've had the time of my _____",
        "answer1": "life",
        "answer2": "night",
        "answer3": "day",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tonight I gotta cut loose, footloose. Kick off your _____ shoes",
        "answer1": "Sunday",
        "answer2": "dancing",
        "answer3": "Monday",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Where troubles melt like lemon drops away above the chimney tops, that's where you'll find _____",
        "answer1": "them",
        "answer2": "me",
        "answer3": "us",
        "correctAnswer": 2 
    },
    {
        "question": "As you _____ on by, will you call my name?",
        "answer1": "run",
        "answer2": "dance",
        "answer3": "walk",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Near, far, wherever you are, I believe that the _____ does go on",
        "answer1": "heart",
        "answer2": "soul",
        "answer3": "love",
        "correctAnswer": 1 
    }
]